[{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is IETF :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"Is Apple_Filing_Protocol :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Apple_Filing_Protocol :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"Is Session :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"Is Session :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"Is Class_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"Is eMail :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is VOIP :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is RFC :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"Is eMail :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is VOIP :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is RFC :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"Is Intranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"questionBody":"Is Intranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"Is Malicious_Software :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Modification :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Integrity :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Availablity :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Cryptography :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Passive_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is System_Security :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Confidentiality :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Interception :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Interruption :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Fabrication :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is Symmetrie_Encryption :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"How many number_of_layers is IP_Suite connected with ?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"4","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"8","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 8 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 8 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"12","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 12 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 12 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"16","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 16 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 16 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"}],"strategy":"Datatype-property-based","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Bandwidth?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with superclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Computer_Networks?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the incorrect answer is due to the following : scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the incorrect answer is due to the following : sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Security?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why interrr is the incorrect answer is due to the following : interrr is Interruption"},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why integ is the incorrect answer is due to the following : integ is Integrity"},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why confid is the incorrect answer is due to the following : confid is Confidentiality"},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why modi is the incorrect answer is due to the following : modi is Modification"},{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why availabilty is the incorrect answer is due to the following : availabilty is Availablity"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Scope?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s1 is Extranet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Extranet?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with disjoint sibling classes","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following ia a function of the Bridge?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Translation_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Modem","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Modem is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Modem doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Router","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Router is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Router doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Switch","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switch is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Switch doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Object-property-based","bloomLvl":"Comprehension","keyFeedback":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Open Systems Interconnection","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why OSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model Open Systems InterconnectionOSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Flooders","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Flooders is incorrect answer is due to the following: Flooders  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Star_Mesh is incorrect answer is due to the following: Star_Mesh  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Loaded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Loaded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IP_Suite is incorrect answer is due to the following: IP_Suite  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bonded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bonded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Infrared is incorrect answer is due to the following: Infrared  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Scope is incorrect answer is due to the following: Scope  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SVOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SVOIP  is Secure Voice over IP"},{"id":0,"text":"Switched","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switched is incorrect answer is due to the following: Switched  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why ATM_Layer is incorrect answer is due to the following: ATM_Layer  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyOSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــRemote Desktop Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDPRemote Desktop ProtocolRDP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: LDAP  is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCPMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)MGCP"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: CMAC  is Cipher-based message authentication code"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyMGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Network Management Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMPSimple Network Management ProtocolSNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SFTP  is SSH File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Object Access Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAPSimple Object Access ProtocolSOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــdirect sequence spread spectrum","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is correct answer is due to the following: DSSSdirect sequence spread spectrumDSSS"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDSSS is correct answer is due to the following: DSSS is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Real Time Streaming Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is correct answer is due to the following: RTSP Real Time Streaming ProtocolRTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"TLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: TLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRTSP is correct answer is due to the following: RTSP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــFile Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is correct answer is due to the following: FTPFile Transfer ProtocolFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFTP is correct answer is due to the following: FTP is File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــVoice over Internet Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is correct answer is due to the following: VOIPVoice over Internet ProtocolVOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: VOIP is Voice over Internet Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Building Automation and Control Networks","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BACnet","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why BACnet is correct answer is due to the following: BACnet Building Automation and Control NetworksBACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Ethernet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Ethernet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Internet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Internet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Internet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Telnet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Telnet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Telnet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Intranet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Intranet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Intranet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bandwidth","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bandwidth is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bandwidth  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Brouter is incorrect answer is due to the following: Brouter  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Permanent is incorrect answer is due to the following: Permanent  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Honeypots is incorrect answer is due to the following: Honeypots  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bonded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bonded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Extranet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Extranet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Integrity","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Integrity is incorrect answer is due to the following: Integrity  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Gnutella","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Gnutella is incorrect answer is due to the following: Gnutella  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyBACnet is correct answer is due to the following: BACnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــHypertext Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HTTP is correct answer is due to the following: HTTPHypertext Transfer ProtocolHTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHTTP is correct answer is due to the following: HTTP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSSH File Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is correct answer is due to the following: SFTPSSH File Transfer ProtocolSFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySFTP is correct answer is due to the following: SFTP is SSH File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Description Protocol (SDP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is correct answer is due to the following: SDPSession Description Protocol (SDP)SDP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySDP is correct answer is due to the following: SDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــfrequency hopping spread spectrum","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is correct answer is due to the following: FHSSfrequency hopping spread spectrumFHSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"NFS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why NFS is incorrect answer is due to the following: NFS  is Network File System"},{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSH  is Secure Shell"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFHSS is correct answer is due to the following: FHSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetwork News Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NNTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NNTPNetwork News Transfer ProtocolNNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NNTP is Network News Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــdenial-of-service attack","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DOS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DOS is correct answer is due to the following: DOSdenial-of-service attackDOS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"DNS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DNS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DNS  is Domain Name System"},{"id":0,"text":"DTLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DTLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DTLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDOS is correct answer is due to the following: DOS is denial-of-service attack"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Mail Transfer Protocol ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is correct answer is due to the following: SMTPSimple Mail Transfer Protocol SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySMTP is correct answer is due to the following: SMTP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ARPANET","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why ARPANET is correct answer is due to the following: ARPANET Advanced Research Projects Agency NetworkARPANET"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASETX","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASETX is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASETX  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET4 is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET4  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET2  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyARPANET is correct answer is due to the following: ARPANET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDomain Name System","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DNS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DNS is correct answer is due to the following: DNSDomain Name SystemDNS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"DOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DOS  is denial-of-service attack"},{"id":0,"text":"DTLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DTLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DTLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDNS is correct answer is due to the following: DNS is Domain Name System"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Engineering Task Force","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is correct answer is due to the following: IETFInternet Engineering Task ForceIETF"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is incorrect answer is due to the following: IPTV  is Internet Protocol television"},{"id":0,"text":"DICT","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DICT is incorrect answer is due to the following: DICT  is Dictionary Server Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIETF is correct answer is due to the following: IETF is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSynchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SDH is correct answer is due to the following: SDHSynchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySDH is correct answer is due to the following: SDH is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــLightweight Directory Access Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is correct answer is due to the following: LDAPLightweight Directory Access ProtocolLDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyLDAP is correct answer is due to the following: LDAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Assigned Numbers Authority","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is correct answer is due to the following: IANAInternet Assigned Numbers AuthorityIANA"},{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAB  is Internet Architecture Board"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIANA is correct answer is due to the following: IANA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Point to Point Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why PPP is correct answer is due to the following: PPP Point to Point ProtocolPPP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyPPP is correct answer is due to the following: PPP is  Point to Point Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSecure Shell","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is correct answer is due to the following: SSHSecure ShellSSH"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDH  is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySSH is correct answer is due to the following: SSH is Secure Shell"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــPost Office Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why POP is correct answer is due to the following: POPPost Office ProtocolPOP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyPOP is correct answer is due to the following: POP is Post Office Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDynamic Host Configuration Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is correct answer is due to the following: DHCPDynamic Host Configuration ProtocolDHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDHCP is correct answer is due to the following: DHCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Architecture Board","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is correct answer is due to the following: IABInternet Architecture BoardIAB"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IAX","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAX is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAX  is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIAB is correct answer is due to the following: IAB is Internet Architecture Board"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ chirp spread spectrum ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why CSS is correct answer is due to the following: CSS chirp spread spectrum CSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyCSS is correct answer is due to the following: CSS is  chirp spread spectrum "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــServer Message Block","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SMB is correct answer is due to the following: SMBServer Message BlockSMB"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"SSB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSB is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSB  is single sideband modulation"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySMB is correct answer is due to the following: SMB is Server Message Block"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Protocol television","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is correct answer is due to the following: IPTVInternet Protocol televisionIPTV"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PPTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PPTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIPTV is correct answer is due to the following: IPTV is Internet Protocol television"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــHyperText Markup Language","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTML","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HTML is correct answer is due to the following: HTMLHyperText Markup LanguageHTML"},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HTTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: HTTP  is Hypertext Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"TDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: TDM  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHTML is correct answer is due to the following: HTML is HyperText Markup Language"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Network Basic Input Output System","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NetBIOS is correct answer is due to the following: NetBIOS Network Basic Input Output SystemNetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Direct_DS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Direct_DS is incorrect answer is due to the following: Direct_DS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Network","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Network is incorrect answer is due to the following: Network  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why JUNOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: JUNOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why ZyNOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: ZyNOS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNetBIOS is correct answer is due to the following: NetBIOS is  Network Basic Input Output System"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDictionary Server Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DICT","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DICT is correct answer is due to the following: DICTDictionary Server ProtocolDICT"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDICT is correct answer is due to the following: DICT is Dictionary Server Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــQuadrature amplitude modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"QAM","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why QAM is correct answer is due to the following: QAMQuadrature amplitude modulationQAM"},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: CMAC  is Cipher-based message authentication code"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: HMAC  is hash message authentication code"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyQAM is correct answer is due to the following: QAM is Quadrature amplitude modulation"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــCipher-based message authentication code","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is correct answer is due to the following: CMACCipher-based message authentication codeCMAC"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"QAM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why QAM is incorrect answer is due to the following: QAM  is Quadrature amplitude modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyCMAC is correct answer is due to the following: CMAC is Cipher-based message authentication code"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Research Task Force","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IRTF","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IRTF is correct answer is due to the following: IRTFInternet Research Task ForceIRTF"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is incorrect answer is due to the following: IPTV  is Internet Protocol television"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIRTF is correct answer is due to the following: IRTF is Internet Research Task Force"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_A","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_A is correct answer is due to the following: Class_AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaClass_A"},{"id":0,"text":"Wireless","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Wireless is incorrect answer is due to the following: Wireless  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_E","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_E is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_E  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Star_Mesh is incorrect answer is due to the following: Star_Mesh  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_Fa","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_Fa is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_Fa  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_D","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_D is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_D  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_C","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_C is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_C  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_F is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_F  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Cells","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Cells is incorrect answer is due to the following: Cells  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Plastics","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Plastics is incorrect answer is due to the following: Plastics  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_B","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_B is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_B  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyClass_A is correct answer is due to the following: Class_A is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــRouting Information Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RIP is correct answer is due to the following: RIPRouting Information ProtocolRIP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: VOIP  is Voice over Internet Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRIP is correct answer is due to the following: RIP is Routing Information Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Initiation Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SIP is correct answer is due to the following: SIPSession Initiation ProtocolSIP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: VOIP  is Voice over Internet Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySIP is correct answer is due to the following: SIP is Session Initiation Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــMultipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MIME","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why MIME is correct answer is due to the following: MIMEMultipurpose Internet Mail ExtensionsMIME"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"MPPE","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MPPE is incorrect answer is due to the following: MPPE  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyMIME is correct answer is due to the following: MIME is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــTime hopping spread spectrum ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"THSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why THSS is correct answer is due to the following: THSSTime hopping spread spectrum THSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"TLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: TLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyTHSS is correct answer is due to the following: THSS is Time hopping spread spectrum "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــFiber to the x","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTX","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTX is correct answer is due to the following: FTTXFiber to the xFTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFTTX is correct answer is due to the following: FTTX is Fiber to the x"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــTrivial File Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TFTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why TFTP is correct answer is due to the following: TFTPTrivial File Transfer ProtocolTFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyTFTP is correct answer is due to the following: TFTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet message access protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is correct answer is due to the following: IMAPInternet message access protocolIMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIMAP is correct answer is due to the following: IMAP is Internet message access protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Traversal Utilities for NAT","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STUN","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why STUN is correct answer is due to the following: STUNSession Traversal Utilities for NATSTUN"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SFTP  is SSH File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySTUN is correct answer is due to the following: STUN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــActive Server Pages","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ASP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why ASP is correct answer is due to the following: ASPActive Server PagesASP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyASP is correct answer is due to the following: ASP is Active Server Pages"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــsingle sideband modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SSB is correct answer is due to the following: SSBsingle sideband modulationSSB"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSH  is Secure Shell"},{"id":0,"text":"SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySSB is correct answer is due to the following: SSB is single sideband modulation"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــwireless local area network","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"WLAN","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why WLAN is correct answer is due to the following: WLANwireless local area networkWLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"AAL","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why AAL is incorrect answer is due to the following: AAL  is ATM Adaptation Layer"},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: LDAP  is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyWLAN is correct answer is due to the following: WLAN is wireless local area network"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــhash message authentication code","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HMAC is correct answer is due to the following: HMAChash message authentication codeHMAC"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"HTML","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HTML is incorrect answer is due to the following: HTML  is HyperText Markup Language"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHMAC is correct answer is due to the following: HMAC is hash message authentication code"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IAX is correct answer is due to the following: IAXInter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)IAX"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAB  is Internet Architecture Board"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIAX is correct answer is due to the following: IAX is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــJavaServer Pages","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"JSP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why JSP is correct answer is due to the following: JSPJavaServer PagesJSP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyJSP is correct answer is due to the following: JSP is JavaServer Pages"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetWare Core Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NCP is correct answer is due to the following: NCPNetWare Core ProtocolNCP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"NNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why NNTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: NNTP  is Network News Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNCP is correct answer is due to the following: NCP is NetWare Core Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــReal-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RTP is correct answer is due to the following: RTPReal-time Transport Protocol (RTP)RTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRTP is correct answer is due to the following: RTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetwork Time Protocol ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NTP is correct answer is due to the following: NTPNetwork Time Protocol NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NTP is Network Time Protocol "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSecure Voice over IP","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: SVOIPSecure Voice over IPSVOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why OSI_Model is incorrect answer is due to the following: OSI_Model  is  Open Systems Interconnection"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IP_Suite is incorrect answer is due to the following: IP_Suite  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: SVOIP is Secure Voice over IP"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــspace modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SM","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SM is correct answer is due to the following: SMspace modulationSM"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"SMB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMB is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMB  is Server Message Block"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySM is correct answer is due to the following: SM is space modulation"}]